Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the Vice-President Records 1937-1946
University of Chicago Library
- C, general, 1943-1944, Carlson, A. J. Carlson, Robert Celotex Corporation Cereal Institute Inc. Cerf, Bennett Chaos Club Chase, Harry Woodburn Cherne, Leo Chicago Bar Association Clark, Alden Clark, Evans Clough, Reginald (Box 18, Folder 16)
- C, general, 1943-1944, Coburn, F. G. Colebaugh, Charles Columbia University Condliffe, J. B. Consumers Research Bulletin Cooper, Mary-Co Couch, W. T. Coudert Brothers Coughlin, Fran Cowan, Rita Cowles Commission Cox, Hugh Crain, G. D. Creamer, Joe Croneis, Carey Cuneo, John Curtin, D. Thomas Curtis, Kenneth Cutler, Zene (Box 18, Folder 17)
- C, general, 1944-1945, Calloway, Joe Cameron, Margaret Carter, Marion Cassidy, Henry Chamberlain Chambers, Robert Chen, Y. C. Chorley, Kenneth Clayton, Will Clemensen's (Box 18, Folder 18)
- C, general, 1944-1945, Cohen, Phil Cohn, Saul Coil, E. J. Cole, Fay-Cooper Commonweal Compton, Arthur Cooke, Dwight Coons, Arthur G. Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs Coughlin, Fran Council on Foreign Relations Cowan, Lois Cowles, Gardner Cox, Mrs. G. Cox, Paul Crane, Jasper Craven, Avery O. Croneis, Carey Crowell, Lucius Crowell, Merle Curtis, John L. Czeisler, Louise (Box 18, Folder 19)
- C, general, 1945-1946, Calkins, Robert Castenholz, W. B. Chicago Round Table of Christians and Jews Colonial Dames Coronet Cotton, H. H. Cowan, Leslie Cowles, Alfred Cowling, Donald (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Carlson, Anton J., 1939-1940 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Carlson, Anton J., including Time cover, correspondence, and article, 1940-1941 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Case, Leland, 1940-1941 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Case, Leland, 1941-1942 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Case, Leland, 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Case, Leland, 1943-1944 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Case, Leland, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Cazalet, Major, Dinner, 22 April, 1941, 1940-1941 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Chalkey, Lyman, 1941-1942 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Chicago Daily Tribune, 1940-1941 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Chicago Sun, 4 December 1941, special edition, 1941-1942 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Chicago Tribune data, 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Christian Century, "From Harper to Hutchins," 23 October 1940, 1940-1941, Folder 7: Citizens Board of Sponsors, Faust, Clarence C., "The College at the University," 30 June 1942, 1941-1942 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Citizens Board of Sponsors, Jacoby, Neil, "War's Effect on, Banking," 5 February 1942, 1941-1942 Folder 9: Citizens Board of Sponsors, Yntema, Theodore, "Impact of Defense Program on Business," 4 December 1941, 1941-1942 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Citizens Board of Sponsors, 1942-1943 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Citizens Board of Sponsors, 1942-1943 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Citizens Board of Sponsors, 1943-1944 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Citizens Board of Sponsors, 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Citizens Board of Sponsors, 1945-1946 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- City Club of Chicago, 1937-1938 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Coil, E. J., Director, National Economic and Social Planning Association, 1937-1938 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- College, 1937-1938 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- College Promotion, 1943-1944 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Colwell, Ernest C., 1943-1944 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Colwell, Ernest C., 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Colwell, Ernest C., 1945-1946 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Committee on Social Studies, University of Chicago Reaction to report of, 1937-1938 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Communications Institute, 1941-1942 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Compton, Arthur, Nobel Prize Movie, 1938-1939 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Compton, Arthur, 1940-1941 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Compton, Arthur, 1941-1942 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Comptroller's Office, 1939-1940 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Comptroller's Office, 1940-1941 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Comptroller's Office, 1941-1942 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Comptroller's Office, 1942-1943 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Comptroller's Office, 1943-1944 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Comptroller's Office, 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Comptroller's Office, 1945-1946 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Contemporary Club, 1938-1939 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Contracts, This Week, 1938-1939 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Corey, Stephen M., 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Corey, Stephen M., 1941-1942 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Corey, Stephen M., 1942-1943 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Corey, Stephen M., 1945-1946 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Courier, Borgese speech and Benton introduction, June 1939, 1938-1939 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Courier, 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Course on writing and English, 1937-1938 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Cover, J. H., 1937-1938 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Cox, Garfield, 1943-1944 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Cox, Garfield, 1944-1945 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Cox, Garfield, 1945-1946 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Cromwell, James H. R., 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Cutler, Preston, 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Cutler, Preston, 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Cutler, Preston, 1941-1942 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Do, general, 1937-1938, Douglas, James H. Jr. Douglas, Paul Dubberstein, Waldo (Box 20, Folder 18)
- D, general, 1938-1939, Daily News Daines, Harvey Darling, Jay N. Daveler, Erle V. Davis, M. L. Deadman, Emmett deBoer, John Delmonico Hotel Denver Post Dictionary of American English Di Franco, Francis (Box 20, Folder 19)
- D, general, 1938-1939, Donnelley, R. R. Douglas, James H. Jr. Douglas, Paul Duncan, Robert F. (Box 20, Folder 20)
- D, general, 1939-1940, Daily Maroon Dantzscher, Walter F. Dart, Juston Davis, Mrs. Davis, Watson Deans Dedmon, Emmett Democratic National Convention Denmark, Jettie J. Denny, George Denwell, Roy K. Dick, Dr. George Dickinson, Robert B. Dietz, David (Box 20, Folder 21)
- D, general, 1939-1940, Documents, Superintendent of Dollard, John Donnelley, R. R. & Sons Dorfman, Ania Douglas, James Dunham, M. Keith (Box 20, Folder 22)
- D, general, 1940-1941, Daily Maroon Dana, Ellis Dancer, H. M. Danish, Miss Darling, J. J. Dart, Justin Davenport, Russell Davidow, Leonard S. Davies, Joseph E. DeHahn, Miss Demster, Arthur DeReutler, Egon DeSavitsch Development, Committee on Dille, John F. Dilley, Charles A. (Box 20, Folder 23)
- D, general, 1940-1941, Dodd, Norman Donnelley, Thomas E. Dorfman, Edmund L. Douglas, William O. Dryer, Bernard Duell, Sloan & Pearce, Inc. DuPont de Nemours Co., Inc. Dynes, Mrs. (Box 20, Folder 24)
- D, general, 1941-1942, Daily Maroon Davis, A. M. Davis, Chester Dennett, D. H. Dennis, Bruce Dennis, Lawrence Denton, Delia Deupree, R. R. DeVry Films Dickinson, John Dierkin, Warren (Box 20, Folder 25)
- D, general, 1941-1942, Donaldson, Hugh Donnelley, Thomas Donovan, Colonel William Douglas, James Douglas, Lewis H. Douglas, Paul Dragstedt, Lester R. Drake, L. J. Dramatic Association Drucker, Peter Duddy, E. A. Dudley, Pendleton Duge, Edna Duncan, Robert (Box 20, Folder 26)
- D, general, 1942-1943, Dart, Justin Davies, Joseph Davis, Yvonne Dean, Joel DeVries, Peter Dickinson, Frank Donley, James L. Doubleday-Doran Douglas, Paul Douglass, Paul E. Dryer, Bernard (Box 20, Folder 27)
- D, general, 1943-1944, Dake, Charles Dalton, W. L. Darrow, Whitney Dart, Justin Davenport, John Davis, Chester Davison, Mrs. C. W. Dempsey, Joseph F. Dick, George F. Dickinson, Laura T. Dillon, John (Box 20, Folder 28)
- D, general, 1942-1943, Donnelley, R. R. Doolittle, Helen Duddy, E. A. Duke University Duncan, Robert Durka, William J. (Box 20, Folder 29)
- D, general, 1944-1945, Danielson, E. D. Davenport, Russell David, Donald DeKruif, Paul Deming, Eli Denniston, W. T. Denny, George C. Dieckmann, Dr. William Diesing, Paul Disney, Walt Disney Mrs. Walt (Box 20, Folder 30)
- D, general, 1944-1945, Dodge, John V. Dominick, W. B. Donnelley, T. E. Dose, Christian B. Douglas, Paul Dubuque, Joseph G. Duddy, E. A. DuPont Magazine Durka, William (Box 20, Folder 31)
- D, general, 1945-1946, Damon, Ralph Dart, Justin David, Donald David, Harry Davidson, Donald DeKruif, Paul De Sola, Alis Dominick, W. B. Douglas, Paul Durbrow, Elbridge (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Daily Maroon, 1937-1938, McNeill, William Rose, Adele (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Daily Maroon, 8 April 1941, Faculty vs. Hutchins on the question of war, 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Daily Maroon, supplement, 14 November 1940, "The New Medievalism", 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Daily Maroon, Alumni Issue, 19 September 1941, 1941-1942 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Das, Taraknath, 1937-1938 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Davis, A. M., 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Davis, Yvonne, 1943-1944 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Davis, Yvonne, 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Davis, Yvonne, 1945-1946 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- DeLee Memorial Trust, 1941-1942 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Dille, John, 1943-1944 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Donnelley, Thomas E., 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Douglas, James, 1940-1941 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Douglas, Lewis, 1940-1941 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Douglas, Paul, 1940-1941 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Douglas, William O., 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Dudley, Pendleton, 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- E, general, 1937-1938, Eaton, Cyrus Eckhart, Percy B. Education, Department of, Franklin Bobbitt Edwards, H. Threlkeld Emerson, Alfred E. Epstein, Max (Box 21, Folder 14)
- E, general, 1938-1939, Eaton, Cyrus Embree, Edwin R. Epstein, Max Epstein, Morris Evans, David (Box 21, Folder 15)
- E, general, 1939-1940, Eaton, Dyrus Editor & Publisher Edmonds, James E. Edmonds, Robert J. Edwards Eggert, Louis O. Ellis, A. Caswell Enrollment Epstein, Max Erpi Classroom Films (Box 21, Folder 16)
- E, general, 1940-1941, Eastman, Fred Eby, Kermit Ediphone Elliott, Edward C. Ellis, Howard Emmerich, Herbert Evans, Mack (Box 21, Folder 17)
- E, general, 1941-1942, Eastman, Fred Eckhardt, Percy B. Edwards, Davis Eggan, Fred Eisley, Trennie Elliott, W. Y. Emerson, Alfred E. Emig, Elmer J. Emmerich, Herbert Epstein, Max Evans, George B. Evans, Silliman Evans Products Everett, David C. (Box 21, Folder 18)
- E, general, 1943-1944, Early, J. W. Eastman, Fred Ellis, Anna Evans, Edward Evans, Mack Evans, Silliman (Box 21, Folder 19)
- E, general, 1944-1945, Eaton, Cyrus Eaton, Mrs. Marie Eckstein, Walter Eggan, Fred Elder, Don Emerson, J. Gordon Emmerich, Herbert Empire Warehouses, Inc. Ernst, Morris Evans, Mack (Box 21, Folder 20)
- E, general, 1945-1946, Eckhardt, George T. Elvinger, Francis Emergency Committee on Station KFI Emmerich, Herbert Engel, Louis Etnyre, Marjorie (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Eaton, Cyrus, 1940-1941 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Eaton, Cyrus, 1941-1942 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Eaton, Cyrus, 1942-1943 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Eaton, Cyrus, 1943-1944 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Economic Club of Detroit, 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Embree, Edwin R., reprint, "In Order of their Eminence", 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Epstein, Max, 1940-1941 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Erpi Classroom Films, Inc., 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- F, general, 1937-1938, Fairweather, George Farrell, Joe Faust, Clarence H. Figueroa, Estaban Fisher, William T. Fortune Fosdick, Raymond B. Fredericks, Charles Freeman, Frank Freeman, Martin Frodin, Reuben Fuller, E. H. (Box 22, Folder 1)
- F, general, 1938-1939, Fackenthal, Frank Faculty, memo re: speakers' bureau Filmack Trailer Company Flook, Lyman Fortune Fosdick, Raymond Francis, Clarence Frank, Margaret Fritz, Edward Frodin, Reuben (Box 22, Folder 2)
- F, general, 1939-1940, Federal Housing Administration Ferguson, Charles E. Ferguson, Stanley Findley Fisher, M. E. Fletcher, Elmer W. Ford, Guy Stanton Fosdick, Raymond Franck, James Frederick, John T. Freshmen, report on Friends of the Library Fuehr, Irma Fuqua, Nelson (Box 22, Folder 3)
- F, general, 1940-1941, Fadiman, Clifton Faherty, Roger Farley, James A. Farr, Miss Farrell, James F.H.A. Federal Radio Education Committee Federal Security Agency Fellowships and Scholarships (Finn, Gladys) Fenn College Field, Henry Field, Marshall Finnegan, Richard Fish, Eleanor Fitzgerald, John D. Flexner, Abraham Flynn, John T. Foreen, Betty Foster, Ben Foundations Franklin, Jay Fraser, Lewis Freeman, John A. Freeman, Martin Friedman, Hortense Friend, Hugo Friends of the Middle Border Frodin, Reuben Fuller, Walter D. (Box 22, Folder 4)
- F, general, 1941-1942, Faculty Exchange Faulkner, Donald Faust, Clarence Feakins, William B. Federal Reserve Bank Feldman, Herbert Fenton, Howard W. Ferguson, Hazel R. Fichtner, C. C. Field, Marshall & Co. Finkelstein, Lewis Finnegan, Richard First Federal Savings and Loan Fischer, Carl A. Fisher, Sol Fitzgerald, John Flanders, Ralph Fly, James L. Flynn, John T. Foley, W. C. Folsom, Marion B. Force, Miss Fordham University Fordney, Lt. Colonel C. L. Fortune Fosdick, H. E. Fosdick, Raymond B. Foster, S. Dudley Francis, Clarence Francisco, Don Francisco, L. Mercer Frankel, Alan Frankel, Jay Frankland, S. W. Freeman, John Friedrich, C. T. Friendly, Edwin Fuqua, Nelson (Box 22, Folder 5)
- F, general, 1942-1943, Fact-Finders Associates Faculty News Bulletin Farm Foundation Faust, Clarence Finn, Gladys Fisher, Edgar Fisher, Robert D. Fontaine, Mrs. Everett Ford, Edsel Ford-Bacon-Davis Fosdick, Raymond Francisco, L. Fuqua, Nelson (Box 22, Folder 6)
- F, general, 1943-1944, Faculty News Bulletin Farm Foundation Faust, Clarence H. Finnegan, Richard Fischer, Louis Fishbein, Morris Fleischman, Harry Fleming, Herbert Foley, Noeen Foundation Press Fredericks, Henry W. Freeman, Miller Friedman, Hortense Furlong, T. R. Furnas, Lee (Box 22, Folder 7)
- F, general, 1944-1945, Facci, Joseph Fadiman, Clifton Fine, Benjamin Finn, Gladys Finegan, Richard Finney, Kay Fischer, Louis Fischer, Ruth Fisher, Edgar J. Flowers, Doris Forrest, Alma G. Forrest, Arthur Fortune Magazine Foster, Maxwell Frace, Ed Francisco, Mercer Frodin, Reuben (Box 22, Folder 8)
- F, general, 1945-1946, Faculty Club Faust, Clarence Field, Marshall Findley, S. W. Finkelstein, Louis Fisher, Walter D. Fletcher, C. Scott Flower, Henry (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Facts about Undergraduates, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Field, Marshall, 1937-1938 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Field, Marshall, 1939-1940 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Field, Marshall, 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Field, Marshall, 1942-1943 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Field, Marshall, 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Field, Marshall, 1944-1945 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, 1937-1938, Miscellaneous correspondence, Robert M. Hutchins, William Benton, Donald Bean, General Program for the Quarter Centennial (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, 1937-1938, Memoranda on Fiftieth Anniversary by John P. Howe after visit to Harvard University and Jerome Green, Date of celebration Theme of anniversary Manager of anniversary Fundraising and the anniversary Program of the anniversary Publications Budget Suggestions (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Bell, Laird, 1937-1938 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Swift, Harold, 1937-1938 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Alumni Campaign, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Memorandum to Committee of Trustees, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Correspondence, general, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Croneis, Carey, suggestions for fundraising, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Duncan, Robert, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Four-way conversation, R. M. Hutchins, John, P. Howe, John F. Moulds, Robert Duncan, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Alumni Bulletin, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Alumni Foundation, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Alumni Magazine, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Bean, Donald P., including organization chart, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Committee Invitation Refusals, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Duncan, Robert F., 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Facts Leaflet, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, "Faster, Faster, Alice", 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, General, including Allen anecdotes, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Hutchins-Utley-Randall Recording, 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Key Statement, "Your University and its Future", 1939-1940 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Marin, Allan, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Mather, William, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, "Message to Alumni", 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, McKinley, Robert, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Morgenstern, William V., 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, "New Frontiers in Education and Research", 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Nuveen, John, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Proposed speech for Alumni meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Public Relations and Steering Committee minutes, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Publicity Committee minutes, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Statement from trustees, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, "A Strange New Struggle – They Want to Come to Chicago", 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, "Tower Topics" – foundation edition, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Winter E. W., 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Woodward, Frederic, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Alumni Foundation Honor Roll (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Alwood, Kenneth B. (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Bean, Donald, 1 July – 31 October, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Bean, Donald, 1 November – 31 December, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Bean, Donald, 2 January – 28 February, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Bean, 1 March – 30 April 1941 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Bean, Donald, 1 May – 30 June, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Bright, Ruth (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Campaign Monthly Reports (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Chicago Daily News rhotogravure section (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Chicago Herald-American (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Citizens Board of Sponsors (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Citizens Board of Sponsors, Standard Club, joint luncheon, 5 June, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Citizens Board of Sponsors, Luncheon, 1 March 1941 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Citizens Board of Sponsors, 25 January 1941 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Citizens Fund News (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Duncan, Robert F. (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Foundation News (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, General, including plan of organization of Citizens Board) (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Hudson, Howard (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Junior Publicity Committee (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Morgenstern, William V. (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Publicity Conference minutes (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Public Relations and Steering Committee meeting minutes (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Proposed Letter to Donors from Robert Maynard Hutchins (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Ranney, George A. (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Ranney Dinner, 25 March 1941 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Thomson, Ruth (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Times newspaper (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, University Week, 6-12 April, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, WGN Radio Series (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Wilson, John A. (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Winter, Edwin W. (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Woodward, Frederic (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Addresses (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Bean, Donald P. 1 July – 3 November 1941 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Benton, William, letter to newspaper and magazine people and their response (Invitation to attend Academic Festival and Symposia) (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Carson Pririe Scott & Co. displays (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Celebration file of printed material (invitations, programs, etc.) (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Citations (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Citizens Board of Sponsors, luncheon, 1 July 1941, "William Rainey Harper" (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Citizens Fund News (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Congratulations (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Contributions to General Campaign (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Honor Roll (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, General and miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Hudson, Howard (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Invitations, Symposia, Programs, Information (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Letter signed by Messrs. Sunny, Donnelley, Ranney and replies (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Morgenstern, William V. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Photographs to guests over Mr. Woodward's signature (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Picture captions (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Publicity Conference minutes (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Ranney, George A. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Symposia Publication plans (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Thomson, Ruth (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Tribune Graphic section (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Weekly Calendar (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Winter, E. W. (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Fiftieth Anniversary, Woodward, F. (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Filbey, Emery T., 1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Filbey, Emery T., 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Filbey, Emery T., 1939-1940 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Filbey, Emery T., 1940-1941 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Filbey, Emery T., 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Filbey, Emery T., 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Filbey, Emery T., 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Filbey, Emery T., 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Fisher, Robert D., 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Fizdale, Tom, 1940-1941 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Fizdale, Tom, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Fizdale, Tom, 1942-1943 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Flagstones, 1939-1940 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Flagstones, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Food Research Institute, 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Football, 1939-1940, Tunis, John, "What Price College Football?" Hutchins, R. M., "Football and College Life" Portfolio on Football, including Tunis article, R. S. Johnson, "Let's Clean House," excerpts from editorials, letter from T. W. Stevenson of Harvard, letter from University of Minnesota Harvard Alumni Bulletin, "Touchdowns and/or Education" "Frankel-y Speaking", Stanley Frankel Oberlin Comes to Town Maroon poll Tunis, "What Shall We Do About Football" O'Brien, Howard Vincent, "All Things Considered" Milwaukee Journal editorial Tribune article Miscellaneous correspondence and quotes from newspapers (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Football, "Test Case at Pitt," Saturday Evening Post, 28 October 1939, 1939-1940 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Football, Wallace, "The Football Laboratory Explodes," Saturday Evening Post, 4 November 1939 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Football, article by Dean Works (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Football, "How to Keep Football Stars in College," Collier's, 4 January 1941 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Football, "Football's White Slaves," Liberty, 2 November 1940 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Football, "They Didn't Need Coaching," Liberty, 12 October 1940 (Box 28, Folder 14)